Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Records - Addendum
Yale University Divinity School Library
World Student Christian Federation Records, Addendum
1897-2015
RG 46C
Yale University Divinity School Library
10
(20 boxes)
This is addendum contains primarily printed WSCF records gathered by the Library up through 2015. It complements the WSCF archives of Record Group No. 46. The World Student Christian Federation was created in 1895 as an international student Christian movement which could encourage and coordinate the work of national student Christian movements.
World's Student Christian Federation
World Student Christian Federation
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The World's Student Christian Federation was created in 1895 to fulfill its founders' vision of an international student
Christian movement which could encourage and coordinate the work of existing national student Christian movements, as well as stimulate the formation of unified student movements in countries where they did not exist.
Scope and Contents
I. Annual Reports
II. General Assemblies
III. Centennial
IV. Executive Committee
V. Publications
VI. Programs
VII. African Regional Office
VIII. Asian Regional Office
IX. European Regional office
X. North American Regional Office
XI. Latin American Regional Office
XII. Audio/Video Material
XIII Addendum - 2002
XIV. Addendum - 2015
These records are complemented by the Archives of the WSCF, WSCF North America Regional Office, and WSCF Board of Trustees held at YDSL, as well as the personal papers of Ruth Harris, Margaret Flory, and Newton Thurber.
Arrangement
I. Annual Reports
II. General Assemblies
III. Centennial
IV. Executive Committee
V. Publications
VI. Programs
VII. African Regional Office
VIII. Asian Regional Office
IX. European Regional office
X. North American Regional Office
XI. Latin American Regional Office
XII. Audio/Video Material
XIII. Addendum - 2002
XIV. Addendum - 2015
Youth in the ecumenical movement; World Student Christian Federation; World's Student Christian Federation
- Annual Reports, Series I
  - Constitution and amendments (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - annual report, 1897-99 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - annual report, 1900-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - annual report, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - annual report, 1917-18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - annual report, 1920-22 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - annual report, 1922-23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - annual report, 1923-24 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - annual report, 1924-25 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - annual report, 1925-26 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - annual report, 1927-28 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - annual report, 1928-29 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - annual report, 1929-30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - annual report, 1930-31 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - annual report, 1935-37 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - annual report, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - annual report, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - annual report, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - annual report, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - annual report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - annual report, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - annual report, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - annual report, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - annual report, 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - annual report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- General Assemblies and Committees, 1928; Series II
  - Minutes, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Federation Handbook, 1928-30 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Report, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Report, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Minutes, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Minutes, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Minutes, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Minutes, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Reports, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Minutes, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Reports: 1, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Reports: 2, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Minutes, 1963-64 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Reports, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Minutes, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Excerpts from Minutes, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Report on the Federation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Reports, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Minutes, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Reports and Minutes, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Minutes, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Minutes, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Minutes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes and reports from Women's pre-assembly, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Centennial Celebration, 1993; Series III
  - Committee Minutes, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Committee Minutes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Centennial Fund, 1990-95 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Events Task Group, 1993-94 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - History Project Minutes, 1990-95 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Poster (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Journal, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Journal, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - General Assembly: A Community of memory and Hope, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Annual Report, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Grey Book: Life of the movements, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Journal of Ecumenical Studies: #3, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Journal of Ecumenical Studies: #4, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Program, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Annual Report, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Program, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Annual Report, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Report on the Consultation in New York, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Executive Committee, 1989-90; Series IV
  - Minutes, 1989-90 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Report, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Minutes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Minutes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Minutes, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Report of general secretary, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Reports, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Program, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Minutes, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Minutes, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Reports, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Minutes, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Reports and Agenda, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Minutes, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Minutes of Officers Meeting, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Minutes, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Report: The Christian Community in the Academic World, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Minutes, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Minutes, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Minutes, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Minutes, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Minutes, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Minutes, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Minutes, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Minutes, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Minutes, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Reports, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Minutes, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Reports, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Minutes, 1930-32 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Minutes, 1926-28 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Minutes, 1924-25 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Minutes, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Minutes, 1920-21 (Box 7, Folder 106)
- Publications, 1991; Series V
  - Dossier: Women's Pre-assembly, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - The Church and the World, by the United Student Christian Council (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Unto a Lively Hope: A Report on the Life of the WSCF (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Christian Witness to a Responsible university, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - AIKYA: National Student paper of India, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - The Intercollegian, Sept 1945 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Federal News Sheet, Vol. X, No. 3, May-June 1950 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Federal news Sheet, Vol. X, No. 4, July-Aug 1950 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Federal News Sheet, Vol. XV, No. 2, March-April1955 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Life and Mission of the Church, Series A1 thru E2 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - What is the WSCF? (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - The Christian Community in the Academic World (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Witnessing to Jesus Christ: a Report on the Life of the WSCF, 1953-56 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Nationalism in the Student World, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - The SCM in the Far Eastern Conflict, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Essence of the Ecumenical Movement, by LA Zander (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - The Ecumenical Task of the SCM (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Social Study and Action in the SCM, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Witnessing in University Communities, 1949-52 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - 50 Years, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Dossier: European Region, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Dossier, No. 5, June 1974 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Dossier, No. 7, Feb. 1975 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Dossier, No. 8, Aug. 1975 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Dossier, Annual Report, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Dossier, No. 12, Aug.1977 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Dossier, Introducing the US (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Dossier, No. 1, May 1984 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Dossier, No. 1, Feb. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Dossier, No. 2, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Dossier, No. 3, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Dossier, No. 4, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Dossier, No. 5, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Dossier, No. 6, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Dossier, No. 7, Jan. 1986 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Dossier, No. 8, Feb. 1986 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Dossier, No. 1, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Dossier, No. 2, Aug. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Dossier, Education for Liberation (Box 8, Folder 145)
- Program Material, 1909; Series VI
  - Report on North China, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 146)
  - Commission on Christian Faith and Life, 1933-34 (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Bible Study, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 148)
  - Day of Prayer, Offering receipts and correspondence, 1940-43 (Box 9, Folder 149)
  - Federation Leaders Response to j. Mott's Three Questions (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - Correspondence and receipts on sell of Emblems, 1941-43 (Box 9, Folder 151)
  - Day of Prayer, Offering receipts and correspondence, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 152)
  - Oslo World Conference Material, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 153)
  - Oslo World Conference of Christian Youth, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 154)
  - Officers Meeting, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 155)
  - Student Conference, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - Communique, 1953-56 (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Officers Meeting, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Strausburgh Teaching Conference: Program Materials, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Strausburgh Teaching Conference: Reports, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Ecumenical Center: Report on Leadership Commission, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Officers Meeting: Minutes, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Schools Newsletter, No.12-15, 1960-61 (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - Schools Newsletter, No. 16-19, and 21, 1962-63 (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Schools Newsletter, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - Officers Meeting: Minutes, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - The Christian Church and Communist Atheism (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Missions: New University for a New Worlds (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - Students and the Life and mission of the Church: A report on the Life of the WSCF, 1956-64 (Box 10, Folder 169)
  - Progress Report on the WSCF, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 170)
  - Life and Mission of the Church: Theological BasisAPUP Regional Conference-Cincinnati OHIO, 1957-8 (Box 10, Folder 171)
  - Missionary Research Library: Limitations of Intellectual Approach, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 172)
  - Report on Ecumenical Relations, Nation Student Legislative Committee, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Missions: Membership Boards (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Missions: Youth and Ecumenical Relationship (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Conference on Mission of Church, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Project List, 1974-5 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Program and Project List, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - Missions: report on Consultation, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - Missions: Reports, 1951-55 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - A history of NESC and NESCC, 1980-86 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - Consultation on Racism, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Jesus Christ-The Reconciler: Report on the Life of the WSCF, 1953-56 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Report of Bible Study Conference, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - Campaign Manual (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Directory, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Directory, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Directory, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - Directory, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Directory, 1962-63 (Box 11, Folder 190)
  - Directory, 1964-65 (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - Directory, 1966-67 (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - Who's Who in the WSCF, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - Directory, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - Directory, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Directory, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - Directory, Regional Offices (Box 11, Folder 197)
  - Perspectives on Students Studying Abroad, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - Program, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 199)
  - Program, 1979-80 (Box 11, Folder 200)
  - Program, 1981-82 (Box 11, Folder 201)
  - Program, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 202)
  - Program, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 203)
  - Program, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 204)
  - Program, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 205)
  - Program, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Women: Commission Report, 1981-90 (Box 12, Folder 207)
  - Women: Participation in the Federation (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - Women: Women in the WSCF, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 209)
  - Women: Pre-Assembly Report, 28th General Assembly (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Women: Gender Equality in WSCF, By Ruth Harris (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Women: Motherland (Box 12, Folder 212)
  - Women: Women Doing Theology (Box 12, Folder 213)
  - Women: minutes of Women's Committee, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 214)
  - Women: Women's Programs (Box 12, Folder 215)
- African Regional Office, 1969-70; Series VII
  - Presence, Vol. 3, No. 1-3, 1969-70 (Box 12, Folder 216)
  - Presence, Vol.2, No.2 (Box 12, Folder 217)
  - Presence: WSCF Executive Committee, 1965-68 (Box 12, Folder 218)
  - Report on Visit to West Africa (Box 12, Folder 219)
  - Africa, the West, and Christianity (Box 12, Folder 220)
  - Discipleship in Africa (Box 12, Folder 221)
  - Africa Newsletter, July 1991Nov. 1991 Dec 1992 (Box 12, Folder 222)
  - West Africa Study Project, No. 4-10 (Box 12, Folder 223)
  - West Africa Study project, No. 1-2 (Box 12, Folder 224)
- Asia\Pacific Regional Office, 1964; Series VIII
  - Second Asian Conference of the Life and Mission of the Church, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 225)
  - South Asian News, No. 7-10, 1975-76 (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - Footnotes, Vol. 2, No. 1 and 3, 1969-70 (Box 12, Folder 227)
  - Praxis: Asia's Newsletter, Vol. V, No.3, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 228)
  - Praxis: Asia's Newsletter, Vol. IV, No. 1, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 229)
  - Praxis: Asia's Newsletter, Vol.II, No.4-5, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 230)
  - Praxis: Asia's Newsletter, Vol. I, No. 7, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 231)
  - Praxis: Asia's Newsletter, Vol. I, No. 5, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 232)
  - Asia's Bengalar Conference, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 233)
  - China Study Group Report, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 234)
  - Asia's Bangkok Committee meeting, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 235)
  - Asian Issues, Vol.2, No. 1, Jan 1983 (Box 13, Folder 236)
  - Regional Reports, 1986-90 (Box 13, Folder 237)
  - CCA-WSCF Joint Program, Dossier 1-2, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 238)
  - The Rise of China: Report of North American Working Party, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 239)
  - The Rise of China: Report of North American Working Party, Vol. I, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 240)
  - The Rise of China: Report of North American Working Party, Vol. II, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 241)
  - Human Resources Development Report, 1982-861989, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 242)
  - CCA-WSCF Consultation Program, 1982, 19851991, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 243)
  - China and the Great Cultural Revolution, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 244)
  - Regional Women's Report, 1986-90 (Box 14, Folder 245)
  - SCM Leaders in Asia: Looking Ahead, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 246)
  - Footnotes: Asian Committee Minutes, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 247)
  - Information and Reports on Asian conference, 1958-59 (Box 14, Folder 248)
  - Dossier: Christian Solidarity (Box 14, Folder 249)
  - Women's Regional Conference: Minutes, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 250)
  - Regional Women's Report: History, Vision, Program, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 251)
  - Asian Conference: God's people in God's World, 1958-59 (Box 14, Folder 252)
- European Regional Office, 1919-20; Series IX
  - German Youth Movement, 1919-20 (Box 14, Folder 253)
  - Articles of WSCF: Germany, 1918-29 (Box 14, Folder 254)
  - Articles of WSCF: French, 1918-29 (Box 14, Folder 255)
  - Articles of WSCF: Netherlands, 1918-29 (Box 14, Folder 256)
  - Weekly Publication of Netherlands' Students (Box 14, Folder 257)
  - Articles of WSCF: Italy, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 258)
  - French Federation of Student Christian Associations, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 259)
  - Annual Report of Student Christian Union in Netherlands, 1916-17 (Box 15, Folder 260)
  - Conference of German Student Union, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 261)
  - Euro-theological Student Conference: Summary Report (Box 15, Folder 262)
  - the Student World: Venite Adoremus, parts III and IV, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 263)
  - The Student World: Correspondence, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 264)
  - Project List, 1975-76 (Box 15, Folder 265)
  - Europe Report, No. 1-3 (Box 15, Folder 266)
  - Newsletter, No. 23-26, and 28, 1980-82 (Box 15, Folder 267)
  - Newsletter, No. 4, 7,9,12,13, and 19-21, 1972-79 (Box 15, Folder 268)
  - French Reports on United States' and England's SCM (Box 15, Folder 269)
  - Up-date, No. 2, 8, 9, and 15 (Box 15, Folder 270)
  - European Conference, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 271)
  - Council of Europe: Beyond the Boundaries (Box 15, Folder 272)
  - Mozaik, No.1-2, 1992; No.1, 1993, 1992-93 (Box 15, Folder 273)
  - Reply to Questionnaire of the WSCF, British SCM, 1922-23 (Box 15, Folder 274)
  - Newsletter: European Women, No. 4, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 275)
  - European Committee: Minutes, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 276)
- North American Office, 1937; Series X
  - USA, Day of Prayer: SCM in New England, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 277)
  - USA, Day of Prayer: SCM in New England, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 278)
  - USA, World Newsletter and Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 279)
  - USA, World Student Service Fund Newsletter (Box 16, Folder 280)
  - USA, Promotional and Fund-raising material (Box 16, Folder 281)
  - Canada, Office Correspondence, 1960's (Box 16, Folder 282)
  - Summer Conference Notes, Lunsberg, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 283)
  - USA, Ecumenical Student Conference, Berkeley, CA, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 284)
  - Regional Office Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 285)
  - USA, Trusties Minutes, 1990's (Box 16, Folder 286)
  - USA, Correspondence of Secretary, 1948-56 (Box 16, Folder 287)
  - USA, WSCF Correspondence Concerning Denominational Summer Conferences, 1940-43 (Box 16, Folder 288)
  - USA, Correspondence of US Office Secretary, 1941-43 (Box 16, Folder 289)
  - USA, Correspondence of Edwin Espy, Regional Secretary, 1942-43 (Box 16, Folder 290)
  - USA, Federation Correspondence with Helen Morton, YMCA Secretary, 1937-1940 (Box 17, Folder 291)
  - USA, DW Lyon Report on Federation in China, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 292)
  - USA, CD Hurrey Notes on Trip to Cuba and Jamaica, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 293)
  - USA, Ruth Rouse Notes on Trip to Austria, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 294)
  - USA, Robert Wilder Report on Observation Tour of European States, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 295)
  - USA, Father Kelly and Talbot notes on American Tour, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 296)
  - USA, Getting Educated about Education, by SCM of New England (Box 17, Folder 297)
  - USA, Focus/Latin America, by University Christian Movement (Box 17, Folder 298)
  - Newsletter, Autumn 1976 andFall 1977 (Box 17, Folder 299)
  - One Why is Worth a Thousand What's, by University Christian Movement, May 1969 (Box 17, Folder 300)
  - Press-On, Quarterly Publication, Vol. 1, No.3, Winter 1980 (Box 17, Folder 301)
  - USA, Report on Student Department, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 302)
  - USA, Student Christian Association Movement: A Report on WSCF, 1931-35 (Box 17, Folder 303)
  - USA, SCM of New England, Resource Group, June 1949 (Box 17, Folder 304)
  - USA, Confidential Report on American Colleges, May 1942 (Box 17, Folder 305)
  - USA, Experiment in Ecumenism, by Herluf Jensen, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 306)
- Latin America, Series XI
  - Central America, FUMEC: Vol. 1-3 (Box 17, Folder 307)
  - South America, Chile Dossier, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 308)
- Audio/Video, 1974; Series XII
  - Video: Mercy Oduyoye (Memphis), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 309)
  - Slides: Strasburg Conference, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 310)
  - Slides: Youth Movements (Box 18, Folder 311)
  - Pictures: Oslo Youth Conference, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 312)
  - Pictures: Lundsberg Conference, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 313)
  - Slides: SCM Conferences (Box 18, Folder 314)
  - Pictures: Student Leaders and Conferences (Box 18, Folder 315)
- Addendum 2002, Series XIII
  - Correspondence, minutes, reports, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 316)
  - Re. WSCF General Assembly, Chantilly, France, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 317-319)
  - Re. book and video project on SCM, "By Faith: A Jounrey of the 20th Century Christian Students"; correspondence re. Study Book prepared by John Lindner, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 320)
  - List of affilated and associated movements, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 321)
  - Trustees meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 322-323)
  - Re. Ecumenical Assistance Program, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 324)
  - WSCF Executive Committee meeting, Quito, Ecuador, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 325)
  - "Bible and Theology in the Federation" consultation, Bossey, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 326)
  - "Big E" gathering of students in Europe, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 327)
  - Documents re. women in the WSCF, 1983-1990 (Box 19, Folder 328)
  - Universal Day of Prayer for Students liturgy, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 329)
  - Related organizations: National Christian Youth and Student Congress, Monrovia, Liberia, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 330)
  - Related organizations: Student Christian Movement of India, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 331)
  - Related organizations: Student Christian Movement of Canada, National Council, Halifax, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 332)
  - Related organizations: University Christian Movement in New England, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 333)
- Addendum 2015, Series XIV
  - "A Community of Memory & Hope" - program for Centennial Assembly, Yamoussoukro, Cote d'Ivoire; WSCF Journal Centenary issue, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Red Book Annual reports: 2006, 2007, 2008, 2009-2010, 2011, 2012-2013, 2006-2013 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Senior Friends Gathering, WSCF 34th General Assembly, 2008: "...and your elders shall dream dreams", 2009 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Periodical publications: Federation News, 1960, 1998, 2001, 2002, 2005-2014 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Periodical publications: Student World07: Migration, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Periodical publications: Question (Q.)- issues 1-5, 7, ca.1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes issues on "Struggle in III World", "La Nature de l'Imperialisme Aujourd'hui", "Chile", "Southern Africa"
  - Booklets for Universal Day of Prayer for Student, 2007, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Related to Asia, 1966, 1967, 1969, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Consultation on Ecumenical Strategy in the Universities of Asia; Student World issue on China; Reflections on WSCF delegation's visit to China, Lectures from the Canada-Japan China Seminar
  - Related to Latin America, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    One issue of Fumec Testimonio magazine; Study document for Europe-Latin America and Caribbean Encounter
  - Related to book "Journeys That Opened Up the World: Women, Student Christian Movements, and Social Justice, 1955-1975" and Women's History Consultation (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Related to WSCF archives, 1991, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Senior Friends of WSCF, 2008, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Letter regarding change of date of General Assembly; Farewell message from outgoing General Secretary Christine Housel, 2014, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - WSCF website printout, 2015 March (Box 20, Folder 14)